schoolspecialty.com 2010-11-27

# All of the educational products you've come to know and trust - School Specialty, Inc.

This web site has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site 
  2. User ID and Password 
  3. The organization collecting the information 
  4. How the information is used 
  5. With whom the information may be shared 
  6. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  7. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the control of the web site. 
  8. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 
  9. How you can limit the use and access to the information. 

**By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree please do not use or access this site or our services. School Specialty Educator's Marketplace is a division/subsidiary of School Specialty, Inc. ("School Specialty").** If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact the Customer Service Department of School Specialty by email at [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com). 

**Information Collection and Use**  
School Specialty is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. School Specialty collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We use your information to facilitate the services we provide you in the sale and distribution of products and services that you request. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms & Conditions of Use. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems. You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

**User ID and Password**  
You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password, including fees or expenses related to its misuse. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your School Specialty ID or password to any third parties, with whom you do not wish to be completely liable for their actions. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password and notify us at [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com). 

**Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user may become registered. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name, email address, billing address, authorized users, and budgets). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information and unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

**Order**  
We request information from the user on order forms and supplier agreements. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like budget codes and credit card information). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill user's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this information is used to contact the user.

**Information from Other Sources**  
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site as well as having the ability to take advantage of all of the features of our site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log Files**  
We also collect Non-personally Identifiable Information though our Internet log files, which record data such as IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of the Website. This information may be used to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to monitor the Website's use, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to Personally Identifiable Information for these and other purpose such as personalizing your experience on the website and evaluating our Internet systems. 

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregate demographic information with our suppliers and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual user. 

We and our suppliers may use outside parties for the purposes of fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They might have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Suppliers on our site also have the ability to collect information from users purchasing their goods or services under the School Specialty site. Suppliers of School Specialty agree to be bound by and comply with the terms of this Privacy statement to the same extent that such Privacy Statement shall apply to School Specialty. 

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy business operations or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that the School Specialty division of School Specialty, Inc., or substantially all of its assets or shares is acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use (http://www.schoolspecialty.com/terms.jsp); or protect the rights, property, or safety of School Specialty, our users, or others. We do share such information on a need to know basis with shippers and credit companies when applicable. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

School Specialty gives you access to user information regarding you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. When you update information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such School Specialty features.

For a chart showing what information we collect from or about you, and who has access to that information, please see http://www.schoolspecialty.com/userInformation.jsp

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that School Specialty is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**E-mail List**  
A user may to subscribe our e-mail list. We collect the contact information such as name and email address which we receive at the time of registration.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site may request information from users via voluntary surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect most sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a Customer Service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected access to the company's local area network. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our user's information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

We of course, transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com).

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our users, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

For example, to determine if our users qualify for an open account, we may request a credit report. Once we determine a user's credit-worthiness, this document is stored in a secure environment.

**Special Offers**  
We send all new users and their authorized members a welcoming email to verify passwords and usernames. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we provide the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also provide the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service and update to the site. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email, phone, or on the website, at our option.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by email to [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com). **Choice/Opt-out. Our users are given the facility to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' option so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com).

Unless users of our site request by e-mail at [info@schoolspecialty.com](mailto:info@schoolspecialty.com) that they receive prior notice before their information is being collected by any outside parties, no such notice will be provided. We provide this option for those users who desire to make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on our website so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy statement under which the information was collected.
